{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "title": "week1",
      "questions": [
        {
          "index": 1,
          "question": "In the word root for conservation, con stands for",
          "options": ["together", "to keep", "house", "manage"],
          "correct": "together"
        },
        {
          "index": 2,
          "question": "“The ability of a single economic actor (or small group of actors) to have a substantial influence on market prices” is known as",
          "options": ["price power", "market power", "externality", "economic power"],
          "correct": "market power"
        },
        {
          "index": 3,
          "question": "“An economy that allocates resources through the decentralised decisions of many firms and households as they interact in markets for goods and services” is a / an",
          "options": ["urban economy", "rural economy", "planned economy", "market economy"],
          "correct": "market economy"
        },
        {
          "index": 4,
          "question": "In the word root for conservation, servare stands for",
          "options": ["together", "to keep", "house", "manage"],
          "correct": "to keep"
        },
        {
          "index": 5,
          "question": "Which of these is true?",
          "options": [
            "Wants are unlimited, resources are unlimited",
            "Wants are limited, resources are limited",
            "Wants are unlimited, resources are limited",
            "Wants are limited, resources are unlimited"
          ],
          "correct": "Wants are unlimited, resources are limited"
        },
        {
          "index": 6,
          "question": "“An increase in the overall level of prices in the economy” is",
          "options": ["inflation", "deflation", "stagflation", "priceflation"],
          "correct": "inflation"
        },
        {
          "index": 7,
          "question": "Phillips curve shows the relation between",
          "options": [
            "profit and loss",
            "marked price and selling price",
            "inflation rate and unemployment rate",
            "electricity consumption and heat output"
          ],
          "correct": "inflation rate and unemployment rate"
        },
        {
          "index": 8,
          "question": "In the word root for Economics, oikos stands for",
          "options": ["together", "to keep", "house", "manage"],
          "correct": "house"
        },
        {
          "index": 9,
          "question": "Most of rational thinking occurs",
          "options": ["before the margin", "at the margin", "after the margin", "none of these"],
          "correct": "at the margin"
        },
        {
          "index": 10,
          "question": "Input costs that do not require an outlay of money are",
          "options": ["explicit costs", "implicit costs", "opportunity costs", "phantom costs"],
          "correct": "implicit costs"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
